<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://timetorain.github.io</id>
    <title>timetorain</title>
    <updated>2020-05-06T13:54:59.127Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://timetorain.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://timetorain.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>这是一个消息平台。|This is a message platfrom.</subtitle>
    <logo>https://timetorain.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://timetorain.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2020, timetorain</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[漏洞报告|Bugs report|ID:Website Bugs 1]]></title>
        <id>https://timetorain.github.io/post/lou-dong-bao-gao-orbugs-reportoridwebsite-bug-1/</id>
        <link href="https://timetorain.github.io/post/lou-dong-bao-gao-orbugs-reportoridwebsite-bug-1/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-05-05T13:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>翻译总是会出现错误。<br>
There are always errors in translation.<br>
ID：Websit Bugs 1<br>
状态|State:未解决|Unresolved</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[漏洞报告|Bugs report|ID:Server Bugs 1]]></title>
        <id>https://timetorain.github.io/post/lou-dong-bao-gao/</id>
        <link href="https://timetorain.github.io/post/lou-dong-bao-gao/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-05-04T14:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>当服务器重开后，进入服务器的出生点总是不正确。<br>
When the server is restarted, the birth point of the server is always incorrect.<br>
ID：Server Bugs 1<br>
状态|State:未解决|Unresolved</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[服务器介绍|Server's introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://timetorain.github.io/post/fu-wu-qi-jie-shao-orservers-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://timetorain.github.io/post/fu-wu-qi-jie-shao-orservers-introduction/">
        </link>
        <updated>2020-05-04T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>这是我本人自建的Minecraft服务器，服务器地址为：timetorain.minehut.gg，服务器暂时只能容纳十人同时进行游戏，管理暂时只有timetorain，以后或许会扩大规模。若你想切换分区，请说/worlds。</p>
<p>服务器分区</p>
<p>大厅_有规则——来到大厅后，所有人都会到达中转站，按下按钮后，你的出生点将会设置于大厅，普通玩家的游戏模式总是冒险模式，进入后，普通玩家总是会会拥有虚弱以及饱和效果。TNT以及TNT矿车被禁止。雕像上加入了屏障。你不能飞行太高。(256格)</p>
<p>生存区_有规则——出生点方圆一百格内普通玩家都会是冒险模式，出了一百格后会更新为生存模式。出生点方圆三十五格之内的苦力怕以及掉落物会被清除，出生点方圆一百格之内普通玩家会拥有虚弱效果，出生点方圆七十五格内会有饱和效果。TNT以及TNT矿车被禁止。雕像上加入了屏障。你不能飞行太高。(256格)</p>
<p>下界_有规则——你不能飞行太高。(256格)</p>
<p>终界_有规则——你不能飞行太高。(256格)</p>
<p>This is the Minecraft server built by myself. The server address is: timetorain.minehut.gg. The server can only hold ten people to play games at the same time. The management is only timetorain for the time being. It may expand in the future. If you want to switch partitions, say / worlds.</p>
<p>Server partition</p>
<p>There are rules in the lobby - when you come to the lobby, everyone will arrive at the transfer station. When you press the button, your birth point will be set in the lobby. The game mode of ordinary players is always adventure mode. When you enter the hall, ordinary players will always have the effect of weakness and saturation. TNT and TNT minecart are prohibited. A barrier was added to the statue.You can't fly too high.(256squares)</p>
<p>There are rules in the survival zone - ordinary players within 100 squares of the birth point will be in adventure mode, and will be updated to survival mode after 100 squares. Coolie fear and falling objects within 35 squares of the birth point will be removed. Ordinary players within 100 squares of the birth point will have weak effect. Players within 75 squares of the birth point will have saturation effect. TNT and TNT minecart are prohibited. A barrier was added to the statue.You can't fly too high.(256squares)</p>
<p>There are rules at the nether - You can't fly too high.(256squares)</p>
<p>There are  rules at the end - You can't fly too high.(256squares)</p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>